GUIDE TO THE AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS COLLECTION MS2352
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Library A/V, 1870-2003, bulk 1921-2003; Series 5; 30 Linear Feet
  - Peale, Norman Vincent AASA 1955 Regional Conventions, 1954-1955; Series 5 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Pease, James, 1958-1963; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Planning for Tomorrow's Schools: Problems and Solutions, May 1993; Series 5 (Box 290, Folder 12)
  - Private School Participation in Chapter 2 of the Education Consolidation and Improvement Act, April 1984; Series 5 (Box 290, Folder 13)
  - Project Teams: Training Education Agencies to Meet Special Education Mandates, 1980; Series 5 (Box 290, Folder 14)
  - Promoting Health Education in Schools, 1985; Series 5 (Box 290, Folder 15)
  - Performing Together: The Arts and Education, 1985; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Performing Together: The Arts and Education, 1985; Series (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Perspectives on Racial Minority and Women School Administrators, 1983; Series (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - The Personnel Evaluation Standards, 1988; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - PI Tipsheet for Proposal Preparation, 2001-2002; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Pillsbury, Howard, 1941; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Phelps, H. Vaugn, 1975; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Phillips, A. Craig, 1966-1974; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Phillips, G. Warren, 1961-1971; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Photo of Rocking Chair, 1995-2002; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Photos - Miscellaneous, 1988; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Plastics, November 1, 1945; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - A Plan of Action for the Next 5 Years, ca. 1970; Series (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - The Point of Beginning: The Local School District, 1958; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Politics & Education: A Series of 12 Essays Focusing on Questions and Issues Around Which Policy Evolves, Undated; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Positive Prevention: Successful Approaches to Preventing Youthful Drug and Alcohol Use, 1985; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - Powers, Tom, 1963-1964; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Pocket-Size Career Education, Undated; Series (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Preliminary Report of the Proceedings of the Dept. of the Superintence, 1919; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 14)
  - Prentice, Justice, 1974; Series 5 (Box 198, Folder 15)
  - Preparation of the American School Superintendency, 1972; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Preparing Schools and School Systems for the 21st Century, 1999; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - Preprint of the Program of the Dept. of the Superintendence, 1931; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - President Bush Video Message, February 14, 1990; Series 5; VHS cassette tape (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Program of the Department of Superintendence Semi-Centennial Meeting 1870-1920, February 23-28, 1920; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Amendments to the Constitution and Bylaws, Committee on a Longer Planned Program for the Department of Superintendence, 1936; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - President Pictures, 1946-1974; Series 5 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - President's Awards and Reception, 1997; Series (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Preparing Students For the 21st Century, 1996; Series (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, General Information [1/5], 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, General Information [2/5], 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, General Information [3/5], 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, General Information [4/5], 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, General Information [5/5], 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Preparation for the American School Superintendency, 1972; Series (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Private Philanthropy, 1963; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Private School Vouchers: What Are the Real Choices, 1996; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Private School Vouchers: What Are the Real Choices?, 1996; Series (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Principles of Effective School District Governance and Administration, 1984; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Principles of Effective School District Governance and Administration, 1984; Series (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Profile of the AASA, 1962; Series (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings American Association of School Administrators Los Angeles Regional Convention, 1952; Series 5 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of School Superintendence: New York Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1890; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Atlanta Meeting, 1904; Series 5 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Atlanta Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1904; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Atlantic Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1918; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Cincinnati Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1903; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Chicago Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1902; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Chicago Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1907; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Detroit Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1916; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Indianapolis Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1910; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Louisville Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1906; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Milwaukee Meeting, 1905; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Milwaukee Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1905; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence: Philadelphia Meeting (NEA) Secretary's Minutes, 1913; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence of the NEA, 1900; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence of the NEA, 1902; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings Department of Superintendence NEA of the U.S., 1927; Series 5 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings Department of Superintendence NEA of the U.S., 1928; Series 5 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings Department of Superintendence NEA of the U.S., 1928; Series 5 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings Department of Superintendence NEA of the U.S., 1933; Series 5 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence of the NEA Respecting State and City School Reports, 1874; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence of the NEA Washington, D.C., 1886; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings of the Dept. of Superintendence of the NEA Washington, D.C., 1887; Series 5 (Box 200, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings of the Meeting of the Department of Superintendence of the NEA, 1922; Series 5 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of the National Association of School Superintendence at a Special Session in March in Washington, D.C., 1870; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the National Education Association, 1893; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings or Official Report of the Dept. of Superintendence, 1934; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the Seventieth Annual Convention AASA, 1940; Series 5 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the Seventy-Second Annual Convention AASA, 1942; Series 5 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the Seventy-Third Annual Convention AASA, 1947; Series 5 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the Seventy-Fourth Annual Convention AASA, 1948; Series 5 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the Seventy-Sixth Annual Convention AASA, 1950; Series 5 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings Wartime Conference on Education AASA, 1944; Series 5 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Professional Administrators for America's Schools, 1960; Series 5 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Profiling Excellence in America's Schools, 1986; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Professional Standards for the Superintendency, 1993; Series 5 (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Professional Standards for the Superintendency, 1993; Series (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Program Development: A Troining Program for Local Association Presidents [Posters], Undated; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Program Development: A Training Program for Local Association Presidents, Undated; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - A Profound Transformation, 1977; Series (Box 286, Folder 11)
  - Project Teams: Team Management Decision Making for Educators and Administrators to Meet Special Education Mandates [slides], Undated; Series (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Proposals for Progress: Promise and Performance, 1972; Series (Box 286, Folder 12)
  - Public Law 94-142: Special Education in Transition, Undated; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations for Administrators, 1988; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - P.S.A. Spots, February, 1975; Series (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Public Law 94-142: Special Education in Transition, Undated; Series (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Positive Prevention Successful Approaches to Preventing Youthful Drug and Alcohol Use, 1985; Series (Box 286, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations for Administrators, 1985; Series (Box 286, Folder 14)
  - Pulitzer Prize-Winning Author's Views: Juan Williams, Undated; Audio cassette tape (Box 297, Folder 11)
  - Quality Goes to School Readings on Quality Management in Education [1 of 2], 1994; Series (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - Quality Goes to School Readings on Quality Management in Education [2 of 2], 1994; Series (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - Quality of Life ... Investing in Our Children's Future, September 1996; Series (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Quest, 1986-1989; Series 5 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Quest for Quality [1/2], 1960; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - Quest for Quality [2/2], 1960; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - Quest for Quality: Two Large Cities [2], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 13)
  - Quest for Quality: Two Suburban Districts [3 and 4], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 14)
  - Quest for Quality: Two Medium Size Industrial City Districts [5 and 6], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 15)
  - Quest for Quality: Two Residential City Districts [7 and 8], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 16)
  - Quest for Quality: Two Small Industrial City Districts [9 and 10], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 17)
  - Quest for Quality: Two County Unit Districts [11 and 12], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 18)
  - Quest for Quality: Four College City Districts [13], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 19)
  - Quest for Quality: Keys to Quality [14], 1960; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 20)
  - The Race We Dare Not Lose [Booklet & Audio Cassette], 1983; Series 5 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - The Race We Dare Not Lose [Slides], 1983; Series 5 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Racial - Ethnic Minorities, 1983; Series (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Racial-Ethic Minorities and Women in School Administration A Selected Bibliography, 1993; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Raising Standards in Schools: Problems and Solutions, 1985; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Raising Achievement Among Minority Students, 1987; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Raising Your Wellness Grade, 1985; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Raising Your Wellness Grade, 1985; Series (Box 286, Folder 15)
  - Ramseyer, John, 1959-1932; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Reading, Writing, Speaking and Listening: Keys to Your Child's School Success, 1999; Series (Box 286, Folder 17)
  - Recommendations for School Districits Regarding Substance Abuse by Students: Joint Statement, September, 1987; Series (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Recent Trends in the Representation of Women and Minorities in School Administration and Problems in Documentation, July 1982; Series (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Redfern, George, 1966-1974; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Redmond, James, 1966; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Reinvest in America, 1992-1993; Series 5 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Religion, Prayer, and Public Education, 1963, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Religion in the Public Schools, 1986; Series (Box 286, Folder 16)
  - Religious Right, 1992-1993; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - The Report of the Committee on the Longer Planned Program for the Department of Superintendence of the National Education Association, February 25, 1936; Series 5 (Box 312, Folder 21)
  - Report of the Committee on the Revision of Departments, 1926; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Report of Committee on Superintendents' Problems, 1919; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Report of Proceedings of Annual Convention, 1925; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - A Report from the 1996-97 Awards for Excellence: Community Collaboration for Children and Youth, 1997; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - A Response to the National Reports: The Superintendent's Can-Do Guide to School Improvement, 1984; Series (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Reporting: Violence, and Other Incidents in Schools, 1981; Series (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Research, 1997-1999; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Resolving Management Conflicts Through Associations, 1972; Series (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Religion in the Public Schools, 1964, 1986; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Restructuring America's Schools, 1989; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Retirement Plan, 1969; Series 2 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - Richards, Harold, 1961-1965; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - The Right Principal for the Right School, 1967; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - The Role of the Principal in Effective Schools: Problems Solutions, 1994; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, Virgil President, 1951-1990; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - The Role of a Consultant in a Superintendency Search, 1983; Series (Box 286, Folder 18)
  - Roles and Relationships School Boards and Superintendents, 1980; Series (Box 286, Folder 19)
  - Roles and Relationships School Boards and Superintendents, 1980; Series (Box 286, Folder 20)
  - Roles and Relationships: School Boards and Superintendents, 1980, 1994; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Roles, Responsibilities, Relationships of the School Board, Superintendent, and Staff, 1963; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Rose, Oscar, 1960-1967; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Rose Lee Hayden "Successful Schools in a Global Age: Why and How", 1982; Series (Box 286, Folder 21)
  - Round Table of National Organizations, 1984-1987; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Royster, William President [1/2], 1982-1986; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Royster, William President [2/2], 1982-1986; Series 5 (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Rungs Are Not For Resting: Upgrading the Profession - Questions & Answers, Undated; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Rural Advisory Committee, 1998; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Rural Conference, 1997-1998; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Rural / Small Schools Conference, 1995; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Salisbury, Arnold President, 1963-1971; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Sallie Mae First Class Teacher Award Video Presentation, 1999; Series 5; VHS Cassette (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Salmon, Paul Executive Director, 1972-1981; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Sandia Report, 1991-1992; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Sargent, Theodore, 1968; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - A Sample Contract, 1990; Series (Box 286, Folder 22)
  - Sample Pilicy: Implementation of Section 504 U.S. Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Undated; Series (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Second General Session, February 20, 1987; Series 5; U-Matic video cassette (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - A Selected Bibliography on Interagency Cooperation, Intergovernmental Relations and Regional Planning in Elementary/Secondary Education and Other Service Fields, 1978; Series (Box 273, Folder 14)
  - A Selected Bibliography on Interagency Cooperation, Intergovernmental Relations and Regional Planning in Elementary/Secondary Education and Other Service Fields, 1978; Series (Box 273, Folder 15)
  - Self-Discipline Helping Students Succeed, 1987; Series (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Seventh Annual American Association of School Administrators Superintendent Salary and Benefit Study 1993 - 1994, Undated; Series (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - SCANS Report, 1992; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Scharer, Norman, 1966-1975; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Scholar in Residence, 1994-1995; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - The Schools and the Depression: A State by State Review, May, 1933; Series (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - School District Organization: Journey That Must Not End, 1962; Series (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - School Governance & Leadership Volume 8 No. 1, Winter, 2013; Series 5 (Box 315, Folder 12)
  - School Energy Crisis: Problems and Solutions, 1977; Series (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Schoolhouse in the Red: Guidebook for Cutting Our Losses, 1992; Series (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - Schoolhouse in the Red: Guidebook for Cutting Our Losses, 1992; Series (Box 273, Folder 13)
  - The School Administrator's Guide to Insurance Buying, 1969; Series (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - School Administrators...Leaders for Learning, 1987; Series 5; VHS Cassette (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - School Administrators View Professional Negotiation, 1966; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - School Administrators Wellstone Award Spins, Undated; Series 5; BETACAM SP video cassette (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - School Age Child Care, 1986; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - School Architecture, 1978; Series (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - School Based Management [1/2], 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - School Based Management [2/2], 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - School - Based Management A Strategy For Better Learning, 1988; Series (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - School-Based Management: A Strategy for Better Learning, 1992; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - The School Board Member in Action, November, 1949; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - School Buildings, 1967-1978; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - School Buildings [Slides and Booklet], 1977; Series (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - School Budgeting: Problems and Solutions, 1982; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - School Building Architectural Directory, 1986; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - School Buildings [Slides and Manual], 1985; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - School Buildings [Slides and Manual], 1984; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - School Buildings: Filmstrip Discussion Manual, 1967, 1971-1973; Series 5 (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - The School Business Administrator, 1970; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - School Check, 1999; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - School District Liability, October, 1953; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - School Energy Crisis: Problems and Solutions, 1977; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - School Energy Management: an Analysis of Energy Conservation Measures Under the Schools nad Hospitals Program, 1982; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - School Health Education Study: A Summary Report, 1964; Series 5 (Box 316, Folder 9)
  - Schools That Make Sense: User's Guide and Resource Materials, 1994; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Slide Set No. 1 and Cassette No. 1, Undated; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - Slide Set. No. 2 and Cassette No. 2, Undated; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Slide Set No. 3 and Cassette No. 3, Undated; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Slide Set No. 4 and Cassette No. 4, Undated; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - School Lunch, 1995; Series 5 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - School Racial Policy, 1966; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - Schools in the Soviet, 1965; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Schools That Make Sense, 1994; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Schoolhouse in the Red, 1991-1992; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Searches (Executive), 1989-1992; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Second General Session: Keynote Address: Richard Riley, "Moving in the Right Direction", Undated; Series 5; VHS video cassette (Box 238, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education, 1988-1991; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Selected References on Safety Education, Undated; Series 5 (Box 315, Folder 11)
  - Selecting Recruiting, and Keeping Excellent Teachers: Problems, Solutions, 1989; Series (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Selecting a Superintendent, 1979; Series (Box 286, Folder 23)
  - Self-Discipline: Helping Students Succeed, 1987; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - A Senate Perspective: Senator Nancy Kassenbaum (R-KS), Undated; Audio cassette tape (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Service to America's Youth: Joint Statement, 1995; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Seventh Annual American Association of School Administrators Superintendent Salary and Benefit Study 1993 -1994 School Year, Undated; Series (Box 286, Folder 24)
  - Sex Equality in Educational Administration, June, 1975; Series (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Sexual Abuse, 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Harassment: The Complete Guide for Administrators, Undated; Series 5 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Harassment: The Complete Guide to Administrators, Undated; Series 5 (Box 247)
  - Shaw, Archibald, 1962-1965; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Singing Superintendents, 1981-1992; Series 5; Audio cassette tapes (Box 306, Folder 13)
  - Singing Superintendents, 1994-2002; Series 5; Audio cassette tape (Box 306, Folder 14)
  - Singing Superintendents - Third General Session - Keynote Address-The American Family, Dan Quayle, Undated; Series 5; VHS cassette tape (Box 306, Folder 15)
  - The Singing Superintendents, Undated; Series 5; VHS cassette tape (Box 306, Folder 17)
  - Site-Based Management & Decision Making: Problems and Solutions, 1994; Series (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Sixth General Session, 1936; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Sixty-Seventh Annual Convention Department of Superintendence, 1937; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Skills for Successful School Leaders: Second Edition, 1994; Series 5 (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - Slide Set No. 5 and Cassette No. 5, Undated; Series 5 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Slide Set No. 6 and Cassette No. 6, Undated; Series 5 (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Sodexho USA & AASA Civic Star Award Indian River SD's Project V.I.L.L.A.G.E., 2003; Series 5; BETACAM SP video cassette (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Some Points to Consider When You Discuss Merit Pay, Undated; Series (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - Some points to Consider When you Discuss Merit Pay, 1983; Series (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Some Points to Make When You Talk About Schools, Undated; Series 5 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Some Points to Make When You Talk About Schools, Undated; Series (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - Some Points to Make When You Talk About the Summit, 1990; Series (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - [Spanish Language Pamphlets], 1982, 1985; Series 5 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Speaking and Writing Skills for Educators, 1993; Series 5 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Speaking and Writing Skills for Educators, 1993; Series (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Special Education, 1985-1987; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Special Memorandum [Hansen v Hobbs Amicus Brief], July 23, 1968; Series 5 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - Spillane, Robert, 1978; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Staff Development in Small and Rural Schools, 1983; Series (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Staff Development: Problems and Solutions, 1986; Series (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Staff Dismissal: Problems & Solutions, 1978; Series (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Staff Development: Problems and Solutions, 1986; Series 5 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Staff Dismissal: Problems and Solutions, 1978; Series 5 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - The State of the American School Superintendency: A Mid-Decade Study, 2007; Series 5 (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - Small Schools Conferences, 1993-1995; Series 5 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Stand for Children, 1996; Series 5 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - State Loans, 1995-1997; Series 5 (Box 174, Folder 1)